homeconstructionimprovement.com 2019-05-29

# Discloser, Disclaimer & Privacy Policies

## Disclaimer & Privacy Policy

This disclaimer, privacy policy and disclosure covers [www.homeconstructionimprovement.com](http://www.homeconstructionimprovement.com/) and all subdirectories and content, collectively known as **Home Construction Improvement** , and operated by Front Steps Media, LLC.

### Disclaimer

Information provided on **Home Construction Improvement** does not constitute endorsement of a particular method or reliable instructions for construction, remodeling, proper use of tools, or other home improvements. You should _**always consult a professional**_ and follow product/tool instructions before undertaking a project that you are not qualified to perform. It is possible that information on this site could omit serious safety and health information, or could even be wholly inaccurate. While we never do this intentionally, it is your responsibility to verify information before undertaking a project. If you make use of information on this site, you agree to assume all risks associated with use of that information.

### Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to www.homeconstructionimprovement.com is important to us.

At www.homeconstructionimprovement.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit www.homeconstructionimprovement.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)  
**  
Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocal) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.  
**  
Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on www.homeconstructionimprovement.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. You can also learn more about opting out of the DART cookie that Google uses by checking out the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html). However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

### Discloser

This policy is valid from 25 February 2010

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact the [owner](http://www.homeconstructionimprovement.com/contact/).

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the blog owners. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

This blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content may not always be identified.

To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org
